messynessychic.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy - Messy Nessy Chic

## Introduction

By accessing any part of https://www.messynessychic.com/ (the “website”) you are agreeing to the terms and conditions described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any of these terms and conditions, you are required to stop using the website immediately as any unauthorized use is a violation of the terms and conditions.

## Collection of Information

This website receives and collects the following categories of personal information that you provide:  
Information collected when you sign up to our newsletters 13Things and Weekend Conversation Starters. Information collected by our website servers: when you visit this website, our website servers may automatically collect your “internet protocol” address and information about the web page that you visited immediately prior to visiting our website.

Information collected when you order products or register for services on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

Cookies: a cookie is a small text file that is sent to your website browser from a website server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit this website, a cookie may be sent to your computer. You can control whether or not you want to accept cookies by adjusting the settings on your website browser.

## Use of Collected Information

The collected information that you provide us may be used to respond to requests for information, answer questions, improve our website, inform visitors of new products and services, and for other informational or other website developmental purposes.

We may also use the information that is collected by our website servers to analyze traffic patterns, record session information, store visitor’s preferences, and identify sources of website traffic to our website.

We may also use cookies to record session information, such as items that visitors add to their online shopping cart when they are on our website.

In the event that our company or its assets are acquired by or merged with a third party, the information collected by our site may be one of the assets transferred.

We may also use the personal information collected on this website to investigate, prevent or take action against suspected illegal activities, problems with this website, or as required by law. We may use the information for legal proceedings, such as responding to subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims as they pertain to this website.

## Processing Data in the EEA

For Users of the website located in the European Economic Area (EEA), all collection and processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

## Data Controller

The website processes Personal Data both as a Processor and as a Controller, as defined in the Directive and the GDPR. The website, which you as a User entered an agreement with when using the website, will be the Controller for User data. As the website adheres to the GDPR, it processes all data provided by its Users from the European Economic Area (EEA) only.

## Third Party Advertisers

The website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Security

Although this website believes that our website hosting services company provides appropriate security measures to protect the information that is collected by this website, we are not responsible for the practices, actions or inactions of that website hosting services company.

## Changes To This Policy

This website reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and without advanced warning, by updating this page. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore review this Privacy Policy every time you visit this site.
